# **A**NDREW FISH

Eugene, OR

Phone: 503-780-1548 | Email: aofish815@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/superfishal | Github: https://github.com/superfishal

Portfolio: In Development

Full-stack web developer with a web development certificate from University of Oregon. Extensive background in event production and service industry management provide strong teamwork and communication skills. Ability to design, build and implement project ideas from inception to deployment. Passionate about user experience, accessibility, security, and web3 ecosystems. Dedicated and self-sufficient with a strong knack for researching new languages and documentation.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Express.js, SQL, NoSQL, MongoDB, Handlebars, React.js, Node.js, Bootstrap, GraphQL and Figma.

#### EXPERIENCE

Manager 2021-2022 Luckey's Club Eugene, OR

Responsible for hiring, training and scheduling staff, making orders, working with the public and handling security issues.

- Implemented a training and daily routine manual for current and future employees.
- Upgraded security and customer experience, handled music bookings and navigated COVID mandates to comply with state regulations.

## Bartender / Server 2018-2022 Viking Braggot Company Eugene, OR

Helped with construction and opening of a new restaurant for the brewery company, as well as starting their catering service. Responsible for customer satisfaction, money handling and making orders on a daily basis.

 Provided food and full bar catering for the 2022 World Track & Field Championships for Asics.

# Owner / Accountant / Performer Proper Sound LLC

2012-Present

Portland, OR

A music, art and experience collective focused on producing small to large events with exceptional sound and meticulously curated artists.

• Grew from small, free events into ticketed, profit generating shows - now booking artists across the US.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Coding Bootcamp Certificate -** University of Oregon

A 24 week intensive full-stack web development bootcamp focused on gaining skills in HTML/CSS, Javascript, databases, MERN-stack, RESTful API's, Command Line and Git.

#### DesignLabs Design 101 Certificate - Online

An 8-week part-time course focused on learning UX/UI fundamentals, using Figma, creating a responsive layout for a mobile app, and designing a personal portfolio.

#### Lane Community College - Eugene, OR

Received EMT-Basic Certification, worked with paramedics, nurses and healthcare workers in an ambulance and hospital setting, as well as for-hire at events and festivals.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### PokeBuilder V2

https://github.com/superfishal/poke-builder-V2 https://pokebuilder-v2.herokuapp.com/

- An online application for searching the entire Pokemon catalog by name or number, users are able to sign in and save 6 Pokemon to their Pokebelt, and delete them from their dashboard.
- I built and styled the pages using Handlebars/Tailwind, set up Javascript button functionality and calling the API to return data, as well as storing
- HTML, Tailwind, Javascript, Node (bcrypt, dotenv, nodemon), Express, Sequelize/SQL, and Handlebars

### The Alpha

https://github.com/superfishal/the-alpha https://rascal-erratic.herokuapp.com/

- A scraper for NFT data minting on the Solana blockchain Magic Eden Launchpad. The
  homepage grabs the current months NFT's, associated data (launchdate, price,
  description, etc.) and displays them on an easy to read card. Users who are logged-in can
  save the NFT to their dashboard and delete them as needed.
- I set up the API call and how they were displayed on the page, worked with GraphQL and the database to be able to save Users and their associated NFT's.
- MongoDB, Node, React, Apollo, Javascript, GraphQL, and Heroku.